Guide to the Maria Mitchell Papers, 1843-2016 (bulk 1853-1889)
Vassar College Libraries Archives and Special Collections
- SERIES X. GLASS PLATE NEGATIVES, 1871-1890
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Poppenheim, 1889 Apr 22 12:07 PM (Neg. Box 21)
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Mace, 1889 May 6 12:30 P.M. (Neg. Box 18)
    Notes: "Slightly hazy."
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Mace, 1889 May 8 [12:12 PM?] (Neg. Box 20)
    Notes: "Negatives developed by Vail."
  - Sunspots, observed by Whitney and Lewi, 1889 May 16 12:08 PM (Neg. Box 18)
    Notes: "Good—group has disappeared since Saturday—Defect in varnishing."
  - Observed by Mace and Kavana, 1889 Dec 6 11:58 AM (Neg. Box 24)
    Notes: "Used 1 oz. Pyro. Poor plate."
  - Observed by Whitney and Canfield, 1889 Dec 14 12:20 PM (Neg. Box 21)
  - Observed by Whitney and Furness, 1890 Nov 24 12:03 PM (Neg. Box 24)
  - Observed by Whitney and Furness, 1890 Nov 25 12:30 PM (Neg. Box 24)
    Notes: "Carbutt. 'A' fail's developer"
  - Observed by Whitney and Furness, 1890 Nov 27 12:00 PM (Neg. Box 24)
  - Observed by Whitney and Furness, 1890 Nov 28 11:03 AM (Neg. Box 12)
  - Observed by Whitney and Furness, 1890 Nov 28 [12:12 PM?] (Neg. Box 24)
  - Observed by Whitney and Furness, 1890 Nov 29 (Neg. Box 11)
  - Observed by Whitney and Furness, 1890 Nov 29 (Neg. Box 24)
  - Sunspots, observed by Mace and [unknown], [no year] Feb 24 [12:12 PM?] (Neg. Box 21)
    Notes: "Spots almost invisible. Perhaps reject."
  - Sunspots, observed by Hodge and Wentworth, [no year] Mar 18 11:45 AM (Neg. Box 23)
  - Observed by Lupton and Arnold, [no year] May 21 (Neg. Box 28)
    Notes: "6. Apparently of doubtful date."
  - Jupiter, observed by [unknown], undated (Neg. Box 3)
    Notes: "Poor Jupiter negative"
  - Saturn, observed by [unknown], undated; [envelope only] (Neg. Box 14)
    Notes: "Saturn negative"
  - Jupiter, observed by [unknown], undated; [envelope only] (Neg. Box 3)
    Notes: "Good Jupiter Negative"